{"Question": "DO + ODD = ARAB", "Answer": "59 + 955 = 1014"}
{"Question": "DO + ODD = DOG", "Answer": "87 + 788 = 875"}
{"Question": "DO + ODD = BALL", "Answer": "89 + 988 = 1077"}
{"Question": "DO + ADD = FOOD", "Answer": "50 + 955 = 1005"}
{"Question": "GO + EGG = ODDS", "Answer": "51 + 955 = 1006"}
{"Question": "OF + TOO = MEET", "Answer": "54 + 955 = 1009"}
{"Question": "GO + EGG = ONCE", "Answer": "81 + 988 = 1069"}
{"Question": "DO + ADD = DAD", "Answer": "90 + 899 = 989"}
{"Question": "AD + ADD = DEEP", "Answer": "91 + 911 = 1002"}
{"Question": "AD + ADD = EVEN", "Answer": "92 + 922 = 1014"}
{"Question": "OF + OFF = MOM", "Answer": "79 + 799 = 878"}
{"Question": "MR + MRS = ROOM", "Answer": "91 + 918 = 1009"}
{"Question": "SO + SEE = NONE", "Answer": "90 + 922 = 1012"}
{"Question": "TO + TOE = EVEN", "Answer": "92 + 921 = 1013"}
{"Question": "BE + BED = ARAB", "Answer": "92 + 927 = 1019"}
{"Question": "HI + HIS = CASH", "Answer": "95 + 954 = 1049"}
{"Question": "DO + DOG = GLAD", "Answer": "98 + 981 = 1079"}
{"Question": "BE + FEE = BOOK", "Answer": "18 + 988 = 1006"}
{"Question": "AS + SEA = EYE", "Answer": "18 + 891 = 909"}
{"Question": "NO + OWN = NOW", "Answer": "54 + 495 = 549"}
{"Question": "AD + DNA = MOON", "Answer": "59 + 945 = 1004"}
{"Question": "NO + OWN = WEEK", "Answer": "89 + 918 = 1007"}
{"Question": "DO + MOM = ODD", "Answer": "79 + 898 = 977"}
{"Question": "BE + SEA = ARAB", "Answer": "65 + 951 = 1016"}
{"Question": "BE + RED = DOOR", "Answer": "28 + 981 = 1009"}
{"Question": "WE + NOW = EVEN", "Answer": "81 + 938 = 1019"}
{"Question": "AM + AIM = MESS", "Answer": "91 + 931 = 1022"}
{"Question": "AD + DAD = EVEN", "Answer": "59 + 959 = 1018"}
{"Question": "ON + NOW = OWN", "Answer": "54 + 450 = 504"}
{"Question": "AS + SAD = ODDS", "Answer": "59 + 950 = 1009"}
{"Question": "AD + DAY = ADD", "Answer": "98 + 890 = 988"}
{"Question": "ME + EYE = MOM", "Answer": "21 + 181 = 202"}
{"Question": "BE + EYE = AWAY", "Answer": "29 + 989 = 1018"}
{"Question": "AD + BAD = ADD", "Answer": "50 + 450 = 500"}
{"Question": "AD + BAD = DEEP", "Answer": "51 + 951 = 1002"}
{"Question": "AS + GAS = SELL", "Answer": "61 + 961 = 1022"}
{"Question": "AT + EAT = TEA", "Answer": "63 + 263 = 326"}
{"Question": "IT + BIT = DATA", "Answer": "75 + 975 = 1050"}
{"Question": "AT + EAT = TEN", "Answer": "76 + 576 = 652"}
{"Question": "AT + CAT = ACT", "Answer": "90 + 890 = 980"}
{"Question": "IE + LIE = ILL", "Answer": "94 + 894 = 988"}
{"Question": "NT + AND = TEEN", "Answer": "51 + 954 = 1005"}
{"Question": "AD + PAN = DEEP", "Answer": "51 + 958 = 1009"}
{"Question": "MR + AIR = ROOM", "Answer": "21 + 981 = 1002"}
